[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Hummingbirds get their interesting name?", "correct_answer": "Because of the noise they produce when they fly", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "They are named after their discoverer, Michael Hummings.", "Because of their singing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these orders the terrestrial planets from smallest to largest by diameter?", "correct_answer": "Mercury, Mars, Venus, Earth", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars, Mercury, Earth, Venus", "Venus, Mercury, Mars, Earth", "Mars, Mercury, Venus, Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2000 movie The Patriot, who was the first of Benjamin Martins kids to die?", "correct_answer": "Thomas", "incorrect_answers": ["Nathan", "Gabriel", "Susan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which branch of botany is concerned with the study of trees and woody plants?", "correct_answer": "Dendrology", "incorrect_answers": ["Forestology", "Topiary", "Arboretology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word means fear of heights?", "correct_answer": "Batophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Bibliophobia", "Botanophobia", "Bathophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous Leporello Catalogue Aria is from which Mozart opera?", "correct_answer": "Don Giovanni", "incorrect_answers": ["La Boheme", "Cosi Fan Tutti", "La Traviata"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color dress was Rosie wearing when her crown was shot off her head in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["red", "lavender", "lime green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The country of Papua New Guinea gained its independence from this country in 1975.", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["Mozambique", "Indonesia", "New Zealand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1997 movie featured Cartesian co-ordinates (the usual type of graph paper) and factoring numbers?", "correct_answer": "Cube", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sphere", "Gleaming the Cube", "Proof"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of fish do the fishermen in the movie The Perfect Storm hunt for?", "correct_answer": "Swordfish", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue marlin", "Tuna", "Sailfish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Blazing Saddles, what was the name of the man Bart got trapped in the quicksand with?", "correct_answer": "Charlie", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim", "Bill", "Mongo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would speak Mandarin as their first language?", "correct_answer": "132", "incorrect_answers": ["26", "74", "432"]}]